Guardian of the universe protecting us against the forces of evil.
宇宙衛士正在保護我們 免受邪惡力量的奴役
He can catch a bullet. Halt a speeding train.
他能接住子彈 他能讓高速行駛中的火車停下來
And leap tall buildings in a single bound.
他縱身一躍就能跳過高樓大廈
- Up in the sky! - Is it a bird? Is it a plane?
- 看天上！ - 那是隻鳥嗎？還是飛機？
A mailman by day. The city's guardian by night.
白天是郵差 夜晚化身為城市衛士
Defending the citizens of New York from the forces of evil.
守護紐約的居民 免受邪惡力量的危害
The world has been protected by a group of extraordinary men and women...
一群超凡的男女守護著這個世界
... who have dedicated themselves to fighting crime.
他們默默奉獻 與罪惡戰鬥
Mysterious traveller from another dimension.
神奇的行者 來自異度空間
He has powers far beyond the capabilities of mere Earthlings.
他擁有地球公民難以想像的超能力
I always wondered why nobody did it before me.
我一直在想 為什麼在我之前沒有人做這些事
I mean, all those comic books, movies, TVshows.
我是說，所有那些漫畫書、電影、電視節目
You'd think that one eccentric loner would have made himself a costume.
你可能會認為一個孤僻的人 才會為自己裝扮
I mean, is everyday life really so exciting?
我是說，是不是每天的生活 真的很有意思呢？
Are schools and offices so thrilling...
上學、下班真的很讓人興奮嗎…
... that I'm the only one who ever fantasized about this?
…是不是只有我對這個感到好奇呢？
Come on, be honest with yourself.
好吧，別騙自己了
At some point in our lives we all wanted to be a superhero.
在生命的某個瞬間 我們都想成為一個超級英雄
That's not me, by the way.
順便說一下，這個不是我
That's some Armenian guy with a history of mental health problems.
這是一個腦子有問題的美國小伙
Who am I?
我是誰？
I'm Kick-Ass.
我就是海扁王
That's me... back before any of this crazy shit happened.
這就是我…如果沒有接下來 發生的不可思議的事情
I guess I was the last person you'd expect to become a superhero.
我猜你們絕不會想到 我會成為一個超級英雄
I'm not saying there was anything wrong with me...
我不是說我有什麼問題…
... but there's nothing special, either.
…只是我看起來沒什麼特別
- Asshole! - I wasn't into sports.
- 混蛋！ - 我體育不行
I wasn't a mathlete or a hard core gamer.
數學不行 電腦也不行
I didn't have a piercing or an eating disorder or 3,000 friends on MySpace.
我身上沒有刺青，飲食正常 也從不在網上瘋狂交友
My only superpower was being invisible to girls.
我唯一的超能力 就是對女孩子隱形
And out of my friends, man, I wasn't even the funny one.
而且不和朋友在一起的時候 我甚至有點悶
Like most people my age, I just existed.
和大多同齡人一樣 我只是存在著
Good morning, class.
同學們早上好
Please open your books to Act Two, Scene Two.
請把課本打開到第二幕第二場
Kick in my bedroom door and you'll probably find me watching TV...
打開我的房門 你也許可以發現我在看電視…
... or talking to my friend Todd on Skype.
…或是和我的朋友托德視頻聊天
- You watching 'Family Guy'? - No.
- 你在看《惡搞之家》？ - 沒有
Me neither. Turn on nippleslip. Com. It's good.
我也沒有，去上奶嘴網，很不錯
Or jerking off, mostly to my English teacher.
或者打飛機 大多數時候意淫我的英語老師
Dave Lizewski. Don't think I haven't noticed you looking at my tits.
戴夫·萊澤斯基，我早發現你在 盯著我的胸部看
Oh, I want your hands all over me, Dave. Please.
哦，快來撫摸我的身體 戴夫，快點
Sure, a lot of what got me through the average school day...
當然，學生時代做過最多的事…
... was making deposits in the whackoff warehouse for later.
…就是打飛機，這是為以後打好基礎
Though, to be honest, it didn't take much to set me off.
老實說，我很容易就興奮起來
I swear, when my hormones balance out...
我保證，如果我的荷爾蒙保持平衡…
... shares in Kleenex are gonna take a dive, man.
…克堣漣J絲牌面巾紙的銷量會陡然下滑
Dave Lizewski. Shouldn't you be looking at 'Hamlet' right now?
戴夫·萊澤斯基，怎麼不在看《哈姆雷特》？
Yes, Mrs Zane.
知道了，贊恩老師
Sorry.
抱歉
But don't get me wrong. I like girls my own age, too.
但也別誤會我 我也喜歡同齡的女孩子
- Especially Katie Deauxma. - Hey, gorgeous.
- 尤其是凱蒂·多爾瑪 - 嘿，美人
Hey.
嘿
Oh... no.
不是
You meant Erika.
你是在和艾麗卡說話
I know. I knew that. I was just kidding.
我明白，我瞭解 我只是開個玩笑
Okay, cool.
好吧，走了
Oh my God.
我的天
Hey, look, I'm Todd's mom.
嘿，看，我是托德的老媽
That's funny. This is your dad.
有意思，我是你老爸
No, that's still my mom, actually.
不，那樣還是我老媽
Oh, the fuck!
哦，搞什麼！
I was just a regular guy.
我只是一個普通人
No radioactive spiders, no refugee status from a doomed alien world.
我不是放射性蜘蛛 也不是來自外星球的難民
You know what? Todd said they do still make Count Chocula.
知道嗎？托德說他們其實 還在生產卡恰克牌麥片粥
They just don't sell it at the store any more.
只是不放在店婼璊F
My mother was killed by an aneurism in the kitchen.
我媽媽在廚房埵]動脈瘤而去世
As opposed to a gunman in the alley.
不是在巷子媥D遇殺手
So if you were hoping for any...
如果你期待看到這樣的情形…
I will avenge you, mother!
媽媽，我會為你報仇！
... you're out of luck.
…只能說你不走運了
In the 18 months since my mother died...
媽媽去世後18個月
... the only epiphany I had was realising that life just goes on.
…我唯一的感悟是 生活一樣在繼續
Did they change the bee's face?
是不是包裝上蜜蜂的臉不一樣了？
No.
沒有
How come nobody's ever tried to be a superhero?
怎麼會沒人想成為超級英雄呢？
Boy, I dunno. Probably because it's fucking impossible, dipshit.
不清楚，可能是因為 這根本不可能
What, putting on a mask and helping people, how's that impossible?
什麼，戴上面具去幫助別人 有什麼不可能的？
That's not superhero, though.
可那並不是超級英雄
Super's like being strongerthan everybody and flying and shit. That's just hero.
超級意味著要比所有人強大，會飛什麼的 你說的只是一個普通的英雄罷了
No, it's not even hero. It's just fucking psycho.
不是，連英雄都稱不上 只是一個神經病
Hello? Bruce Wayne? He didn't have any powers.
那麼？布魯斯·韋恩呢？（蝙蝠俠） 他沒什麼超能力
Yes, but he had all the expensive shit that doesn't exist.
沒錯，可他有很多現實中 根本不存在的昂貴裝備
I thought you meant how come nobody does it in real life?
我想你是說為什麼現實生活六櫌沒有人站出來？
Yeah, Todd, that's what I meant.
對，托德，我就是這個意思
Dude, if anybody did it in real life they'd get their ass kicked.
老兄，如果現實生活中有人這麼做 他們會被人海扁一頓的
- They'd be dead in, like, a day. - A day.
- 他們一天之內就會掛了 - 一天之內
Yeah, okay, I'm not saying they should do it.
好吧，我不是說他們應該這麼做
Ljust can't figure out why nobody does.
我只是不明白為什麼沒人這麼做
Seriously, out of all the millions of people who love superheroes,
真的，幾乎所有人都喜歡超級英雄
you'd think one would give it a try.
應該有個人出來試一試
Jesus, guys, does it not bug you?
老天，你們難道沒有想過嗎？
Why thousands of people wanna be Paris Hilton and nobody wants to be Spiderman?
為什麼成千上萬的人想成為帕奡窗P希爾頓 而沒有人想成為蜘蛛俠？
Yeah, what's with that? She has, like, no tits at all.
對，這是為什麼？ 她的胸部那麼小
Maybe it's a porn tape. He doesn't have a porn tape.
可能是色情影碟的關係 沒看過色情影碟就沒有這些想法
You guys never saw 'One Night In Spiderman'?
你們沒看過《蜘蛛俠的激情一夜》吧？
Oooh, guess who?
哦，看誰來了？
Is it me or do you kinda feel sorry for Chris D'Amico?
我們是不是該同情克奡窗P達米科？
Must be terrible to have a rich dad and everything you want.
有個富爸爸，什麼都能買到 這種生活一定很糟糕
I wish you wouldn't have said anything cos I feel like I'm gonna start crying...
別說了，我都有點想哭了…
The fact that he's always on his own.
事實上他總是一個人
We should, like, talk to him.
我們應該找他聊聊
See if he wants to hang out with us.
看看他是不是願意和我們一起玩
Oh, I didn't say we should talk to him, ljust...
我不是說我們應該找他聊，我只是…
Think about it. Come on, it'd be awesome.
想想看，就這麼做，一定很有意思
If he was ourfriend, noone would everfuck with us again.
如果他成為我們的朋友 別人就不會瞧不起我們了
Go on then, Todd.
你去，托德
- You wanna go talk to him? - No, no, no. No.
- 你想去跟他聊天？ - 不，不
No, you wanna go talk to him? I can move.
不，你想去？ 我讓你
- Dave, Dave should go. - Dave should go.
- 戴夫，應該戴夫去 - 應該戴夫去
- Why? - Dave, you should totally go.
- 為什麼？ - 戴夫，絕對應該你去
- You're a dick. - Don't be afraid, Dave.
- 你這傢伙 - 別害怕，戴夫
You're a pussy.
你這娘們
Fuck off!
滾開！
- Did you spray anything overthere? - I think I might have shat my pants.
- 是不是嚇得尿褲子了？ - 我褲子堻ㄛO大便
If that guy spoke to me like that I would have kicked his ass.
換做是我 我一定海扁他一頓
Todd, when have you ever kicked anyone's ass?
托德，你什麼時候扁過人？
Whatever, man. I would have just gone for his knees.
不管怎樣 我會攻擊他的膝蓋
Well, you're not making sense.
你在胡說些什麼
Well, what I'm saying is the superior force of Batman's Batarang
我是說，蝙蝠俠的飛鏢有超能力
would undoubtedly penetrate the Joker's force field,
一定會穿過小丑的力場
leaving him totally vulnerable to the...
這樣他就沒有能力去反抗…
- All right, and then... but, you know... - Whoa, whoa, whoa Pussy patrol.
- 好吧，然後…，可是，你知道… - 童子軍
Phones. Money.
手機，電話
Dude, not again, come on.
老兄，又來，拜託
Phone.
手機
I don't have one Someone else jacked it last week.
上個星期被搶了
- Pussy. - Give me the bag.
- 混蛋 - 包給我
- It's just comics. - Yo, you wanna get cut?
- 只是漫畫書 - 你想挨刀嗎？
Look at this asshole just watching.
看看這傢伙，就那麼看著
Come on, be honest with yourself.
拜託，別騙自己了
Would you do anything differently?
你不想有所作為嗎？
We see someone in trouble and we wish we could help,
我們看到有人遇到麻煩的時候 我們會想幫忙
but we don't.
可是我們沒有
The world I lived in... heroes only existed in comic books.
我生活的這個世界… 英雄只存在在漫畫書堶
I guess that would have been okay if bad guys were make-believe, too.
我想這樣也沒有關係 只要壞人也是虛構的就好
But they're not.
可是壞人真的存在
Frankie, I'm telling you, man, I swear I'm not making this up.
弗蘭克，我告訴你 我發誓我沒有說謊
This fucking guy comes out of nowhere.
那個混蛋不知道從哪冒出來的
Kicks our asses and steals all the coke.
海扁了我一頓然後偷走了所有的毒品
- The guy that looks like Batman? - I didn't say he looked like Batman.
- 那個傢伙是不是長得像蝙蝠俠一樣？ - 我沒說他長得像蝙蝠俠
You did Tre, you said the guy looked like Batman.
你說了，特爾 你說了那傢伙像蝙蝠俠
- He said like a mask and stuff. - And a cape.
- 他是說了面具什麼的 - 還有一個披風
Yeah, like Batman.
對，蝙蝠俠
I didn't say "like Batman". I never said "Batman".
我沒有說「像蝙蝠俠」 我從沒有說過「蝙蝠俠」
Okay.
好吧
Let me tell you the problem I got with that, Tre.
我跟你說，特爾
Our mole with the Russians tells things a little different.
俄羅斯人那邊的內應 可不是這麼說的
According to him, you sold him my coke and you took the money.
他說，你把毒品賣給他 然後吞了那筆錢
That's a fucking lie!
他在胡說八道！
I can't believe that you would believe this shit from a fucking Russian, man!
你竟然相信一個 該死的俄羅斯人的話
Let me see, Tre, what's more likely, huh?
我想想，特爾 那到底是怎麼回事呢？
That you're a greedy little cock-sucker or all my coke was stolen by Superman?
是你這個貪心的傢伙拿走了貨 還是我的貨都被蝙蝠俠偷走了？
- Batman. - I never said Batman!
- 蝙蝠俠 - 我沒說是蝙蝠俠
Enough!
夠了！
My son is waiting to go to the movies and I ain't gonna disappoint him.
我兒子還在等著我去看電影 我可不想讓他失望
Joe, you're in charge.
喬，交給你
That's gotta be the worst fucking excuse I ever heard, Tre.
這是我聽過的最可笑的借口，特爾
- Sorry you had to wait, buddy. - The movie is starting in 10 minutes.
- 兒子，讓你久等了 - 電影還有十分鐘就開場了
It's okay, we're cool.
沒事，我們出發吧
- We're only gonna miss the trailers. - Yeah, but I wanna get some popcorn.
- 我們只是會錯過預告片罷了 - 是的，我還想要買爆米花
When we get in there, get Chris some popcorn. Okay?
我們到了就給克奡絮R爆米花，知道嗎？
What d'you wanna drink?
喝什麼呢？
- You want a Pepsi? - Yeah, that's fine.
- 百事可樂？ - 好，沒問題
Get him a Pepsi and I'll have an Icee. Mixed.
再買一杯百事可樂 我要一杯刨冰飲料，混合味的
Like when they mix the red one and the blue one.
就紅藍混合的那種
And a pack of Twizzlers.
再要一包糖果
The comic books had it wrong.
漫畫書說的不對
It didn't take a trauma or cosmic rays or a power ring to make a superhero.
成為超級英雄不需要 痛苦經歷、宇宙射線或是能量戒指
Just the perfect combination of optimism and naivety.
只需要樂觀和天真的結合
You are fucking awesome.
你太帥了
Come on then, bring it on!
來啊，不怕你！
- Daddy, I'm scared. - Come on, Mindy. Honey.
- 老爸，我很害怕 - 別怕，明蒂，寶貝
Be a big girl now. There's nothing to be afraid of.
你已經長大了 沒什麼好怕的
- Is it gonna hurt bad? - Oh, child.
- 是不是會很痛？ - 孩子
Only for a second, sugar.
只是一秒鐘而已，寶貝
A handgun bullet travels at more than...
手槍子彈的速度超過…
- 700 miles an hour.
- 每小時700公里
So at close range, like this, the force is gonna take you off yourfeet for sure...
所以，這麼短的距離內 當然你會被擊倒…
...but it's really no more painful than a punch in the chest.
…可那也不會比望胸口挨拳頭還痛
I hate getting punched in the chest.
我討厭胸口挨拳頭
You're gonna be fine, baby doll.
你會沒事的，小寶貝
How was that? Not so bad.
怎麼樣？不錯
Kinda fun, huh? Now you know how it feels.
是不是很有趣？ 你現在知道是什麼感覺了
You won't be scared when some junkie asshole pulls a Glock.
如果有哪個癮君子拔出手槍 你也不會感到害怕了
- I wouldn't have been scared anyways. - That's my girl.
- 怎麼著我都不會害怕的 - 這才是我的好女兒
All right, up you get. Come on.
好吧，站起來，快
Two more rounds and then home.
再來兩次，然後回家
- Again? - Uh-huh.
還來？
Only if we can go by the bowling alley on the way back.
那好，但是我要在回去的路上 去一趟保齡球場
- The bowling alley? - Yeah. And ice-cream after.
- 保齡球場？ - 對，然後還要吃冰激凌
Okay. Two more rounds. No wincing...
好吧，再來兩次 不許躲開…
...no whining, and you got yourself a deal, young lady.
…不許大叫 就這麼說定了，小姑娘
Yeah! I'm gonna get a hot fudge sundae.
耶！我要一個巧克力聖代
Good call, baby doll.
準備好了，小寶貝
So, have you thought about what you might want foryour birthday?
有沒有想過想要什麼生日禮物？
Can I get a puppy?
能不能要一個小狗？
- You wanna get a dog? - Yeah, a cuddly fluffy one.
- 你想要一個小狗？ - 對，一個可愛的毛茸茸的小狗
And a Bratz Moviestar Makeover Sasha.
還要一個像電影明星的寶拉茲娃娃
I'm just fucking with you, Daddy.
我跟你開玩笑呢，老爸
Look, I'll have a Benchmade model-42 butterfly knife.
我想要一個手工制的42型號蝴蝶刀
Oh, child. You always knock me for a loop.
寶貝，你總是戲弄我
- You know what? - What?
- 知道嗎？ - 什麼？
- I'm gonna get you two. - Two?
- 我會給你兩個 - 兩個？
One Balisong. Two Balisong. That's what you get.
一個菲律賓蝴蝶刀 兩個菲律賓蝴蝶刀，送給你的禮物
The glass of fashion and the mould of form.
時代的明鏡 習俗的模式
The observed of all observers, quite, quite down!
眾所囑目者 已經被遺忘！
And I, of ladies most deject and wretched...
而我，一個沮喪不幸的女性
I'll be honest,
老實說
there wasn't a whole lot of crime-fighting in those first few weeks.
起初的幾個星期 並沒有太多與罪惡戰鬥的場景
But even so, my new vocation kept me plenty busy.
即使這樣，我的新使命 也讓我很忙
Shit.
靠
I called it preparation.
我稱之為準備工作
But if you called it fantasizing, it would have been hard to argue.
可是如果你認為這是白日夢 也很難解釋清楚
All I knew was I'd never felt so good about myself.
我所知道的是 我從沒有這麼自信過
Fuck!
我靠！
Okay, maybe I was still in the beta testing phase.
好吧，我還是處於測試階段
But it was a start.
但這是一個開始
What the fuck are you looking at?
你小子在看什麼呢？
- Nothing. - Get the fuck out of here!
- 沒什麼 - 快滾遠點！
Like every serial killer already knew,
正如每個殺人狂所知道的那樣
eventually fantasizing just doesn't do it for you any more.
最終白日夢一定會成為現實
It was time to engage.
是時候開始行動了
Hurry up, man.
快點，老兄
What the fuck?
怎麼回事？
The fuck you looking at?
你在看什麼？
I said what the fuck are you looking at?
我說你小子在看什麼？
Two cheap shit losers screwing with a car...
兩個無賴在偷車…
...that someone probably worked their ass off to pay for.
…我來整治你們
- Say what? - Leave it be, man.
- 說什麼？ - 由他去
This motherfucker's obviously high.
很明顯這個兔崽子一定大腦發熱了
I'm not high. Ljust think it sucks you guys think you can do what you want.
我沒有大腦發熱 你們這些無法無天的傢伙
Just walk away from the car and we can forget about this.
趕緊走開，我就不再追究
You're crazy, man.
你瘋了，老兄
Fuck this shit.
扁他
- Shit. - Let's get out of here.
- 糟了 - 快離開這
I came round long enough to beg the medic not to tell anybody about the costume.
我想通了，懇求醫生不要告訴別人 制服的事情
He promised he wouldn't.
他保證不會這麼做
All I knew was my dad was gonna kill me.
我想老爸一定想殺了我
Why can't I have a gun? I'm a security guard.
為什麼我不能配槍？ 我是警衛
You're a doorman now. You don't get a gun no more.
你現在是門衛 你沒有槍了
I look like a putz.
我看起來就像個傻瓜
You look sharp. All them buttons. Do your job, open the fucking door.
你看起來很機警，全都扣上 做事，把門打開
Have a nice day.
祝您愉快
- Good morning, Frank. - Hey, Joe, how you doing?
- 早上好， - 嘿，喬，你好嗎？
Great.
很好
- Want some coffee? - Maybe later.
- 來點咖啡？ - 再說吧
- Morning, Ange. - Morning.
- 早，安吉 - 早
- Chris. - Morning, Joe.
- 克奡 - 早，喬
Frank, we got a thing.
弗蘭克，有點事情
It's a big thing, Frank.
很重要，弗蘭克
Okay.
好的
- Sorry, hon. - Do what you gotta do.
- 抱歉，親愛的 - 正事要緊
- Chris, where do you think you're going? - I gotta talk to dad.
- 克奡窗A你要去哪？ - 我去找爸門媏談
Christopher.
克奡策咱
Frank, honey.
弗蘭克，寶貝
Where do you think you're going?
你要去哪？
I don't mind you talking business. I was just gonna sit quietly.
我不介意你談正事 我會安安靜靜坐著
I should probably start learning this stuff anyway.
也許我是時候學習這些東西了
Hey, go finish your oatmeal.
嘿，快去吃完你的燕麥片
God-dammit, I'm gonna be 18 in 8 months, for Christ sakes.
真是的，我再過八個月就18歲了
Take a seat.
坐
So what's the problem?
怎麼了？
Our Russian says that Tre just sold him another 5 K's at half price.
那個俄羅斯人說特爾以半價 又賣給他5公斤貨
- Which Tre? Tre Tre? - Right. Dead Tre.
- 哪個特爾？特爾·特爾？ - 對，已經死了的特爾
So now I'm getting fucked in the ass by a ghost?
所以我現在是見鬼了？
Or Tre was telling the truth.
也許特爾沒有說謊
What, this is my choice? I gotta believe in ghosts or superheroes?
什麼，就這樣？ 鬼魂，超級英雄？
Not the part about the superhero, Frankie.
不是什麼超級英雄，弗蘭克
Just that he might have really been gaffled by somebody.
他可能確實被人陷害了
I think we better invite our Russian overfor a friendly chat.
我想我們該請這個俄羅斯人過來 好好談談
See what's really going on.
看看到底發生了什麼事
Hey, early birdie. You beat me to it.
嘿，早起的小鳥 被你搶先了
I wanted to get you breakfast this morning.
本來我想今天早上給你買早餐的
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
生日快樂，寶貝
Check this out.
打開看看
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
哦，謝謝，謝謝，謝謝
Oh my gosh! Dad.
太棒了，老爸
Wow. Watch, Dad.
哇，看，老爸
Okay, pop quiz. What's the proper name for one of those?
做個小測驗 這種刀叫什麼名字？
Easy: Balisong. It's Filipino. Ask me another.
簡單，菲律賓蝴蝶刀 再問一個
Excellent, good.
很好，很好
The AR15 was a lighter...
AR15是一個較輕的…
...smaller calibre version of what design?
…較小口徑的什麼設計？
Eugene Stoner's AR10. Now give me a hard one.
史東爾的AR10 問個難點的
The name of...
吳宇森的…
...John Woo's first full-length feature?
…第一部長片叫什麼？
'Tie Han Rou Qing'. 'The Young Dragons'.
《鐵漢柔情》
Daddy, look.
老爸，看
Hey, come on, you're not looking.
嘿，快看
The point is some fucker is killing our guys.
有個混蛋正在對付我們
And until we find out who that is,
在我們找出這個人之前
I don't wanna see any of you bitches sitting around on your asses, all right?!
我不想看到你們傻乎乎地坐著 聽到了嗎？
What the fuck d'you...
你他媽的…
Hello.
喂
Hey, Joe, yeah.
嘿，喬，是的
No, he's just training right now. One second.
不在，他正在練功呢 等等
Dad. Phone.
老爸，電話
Dad, the phone's foryou.
老爸，找你的
- Who is it? - It's Joe.
- 誰找我？ - 喬
What's the problem?
怎麼了？
Yeah, Frank...
弗蘭克…
Turns out we ain't got the vice here no more.
這堥S有老虎鉗了
- Really? - Uh-uh.
是嗎？
But we do got a brand new industrial microwave -they use it fortreating the lumber.
但這兒有一個工業微波爐 他們用來處理木材的
Well, that is neat.
很好
I think you must be confusing me with someone who
我不想聽到
gives a shit about the fucking lumber!
什麼關於木材的事
- Yeah, o-okay. All right, Frank. - Now quit bugging me and
- 是，好的，弗蘭克 - 別再煩我
- All right, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, okay? I... - get the fucking rest of the information.
- 好的，對不起，好的，我… - 別再說這些沒用的
All right, okay.
好的
Right, come on, go ahead.
好吧，我們過去
Hey, look, the guys tell me he's Tre Fernandez.
嘿，聽到了嗎，這個傢伙 告訴我那個人是特爾·菲爾蘭德斯
What do I know, huh?
我怎麼知道？
- Shut up. - Now you say Fernandez is dead.
- 閉嘴 - 現在你又說菲爾蘭德斯死了
- Okay, he lie. - Get inside. Shut up.
- 是他撒謊了 - 進去，閉嘴
- He lie about... - Fucking mamaluke...
- 他說謊了… - 該死的傢伙
This work like a regular microwave?
這個是不是像普通微波爐那樣用？
Fuck do I know? We're not making a Hungry Man dinner. Just turn it on.
我怎麼知道？我們不是在做人肉餐 快點打開
Here we go.
好了
Okay, I wanna know who sold you our coke.
我想知道誰把貨賣給你的
And don't tell me somebody who's dead this time.
別再告訴我一個死人的名字
Can he hearyou? I don't think he can hearyou.
他能聽見你說話嗎？ 我想他可能聽不見
I said who really sold you our coke?
我說到底是誰賣給你的？
Who sold...
誰賣給…
...you... our... coke?
…你…我們的…貨？
Oh, shit! Shit!
哦，靠！
This is awesome!
太奇妙了！
I look like fricking Wolverine.
我看起來就像金剛狼
You still have that metal detector at your school?
學校那個金屬探測器還在？
Yeah. It's gonna have a meltdown.
對，沒事的
Dave, I need to ask you something.
戴夫，我問你點事
Okay.
好的
The police report. They found you naked.
警察說他們發現你的時候 你什麼衣服都沒穿
You said you didn't remember why.
你說你不記得怎麼回事了
The muggers, they didn't...
那些搶劫犯，他們沒有…
What?
什麼
No. Jesus. No, I... I wasn't even...
沒有，我的天 沒有，我…我都沒有…
In the ambulance they threw my clothes away because of the blood.
醫生在救護車塈漰琲漲蝒A扔掉了 因為上面都是血
Okay, okay.
好的，好的
Seemed like no time at all before I was back on my feet.
似乎很快我就恢復了正常的生活
- Dave's what? - Keep it down.
- 戴夫怎麼了？ - 小聲點
Apart from some messed-up nerve endings, the doctors fixed me up pretty good.
除了神經末梢有點混亂 手術很成功
- Did you feel that? - No.
- 有感覺嗎？ - 沒有
You're like fucking Jason Bourne or something, man. That owns.
你現在就像超級間諜傑森·鮑恩，真的
- How about that? - No, Marty.
- 這樣呢？ - 沒有感覺，馬蒂
Give it a fucking rest.
消停一會吧
I've only been back like half a day and
我才回來半天
you're already making me kinda miss the hospital.
你們就讓我懷念醫院了
He's right. I'm sorry. I'm acting totally childish.
他說的沒錯，抱歉 我太幼稚了
- Stop with the fork. - Watch this.
- 別再擺弄叉子了 - 試試這個
Hey.
嘿
Dave, hey.
戴夫，嘿
Oh, hey.
哦，嘿
How are you? You look better.
怎麼樣了？看起來好多了
I'm good. Yeah, much better.
我很好，是的，好多了
You're into comic books, aren't you?
你很喜歡看漫畫書，對吧？
Well, me and Erika sometimes hang out after school
我和艾麗卡有時候放學後
at this really great store -Atomic Comics.
會去一個很棒的店，原子漫畫店
They make the best white chocolate milk-a-latte.
那兒的加奶咖啡很好喝
Yeah?
是嗎？
I could buy you one sometime if you need someone to talk to.
如果你想要找人聊天 我可以請你去喝
- Sure. Thank you. - Okay.
- 當然可以，謝謝 - 就這麼說
Sweet. Well, I'll see you later.
很好，一會見
- Did you see that? - Yeah?
看到了嗎？
Katie Deauxma just offered to buy me coffee.
凱蒂說要請我喝咖啡
Yeah. You know, I really don't think that's what it looks like.
你知道嗎，我覺得有點古怪
- What are you talking about? - The point is...
- 你說什麼呢？ - 問題是…
...Katie's all about the lame ducks.
…凱蒂是個投機的人
What's this got to do with me?
這跟我有什麼關係？
I've been trying to figure out how to tell you this.
我弄明白之後再告訴你
- There's a rumour going around... - Right.
- 有謠言說… - 沒錯
...that you... - What?
- 你… - 什麼？
...are gay. - Gay?!
- 是同性戀 - 同性戀？
- What kind of rumour's that? - Well, getting mugged and...
- 太離譜了吧？ - 被人打劫，然後…
- You guys have been mugged. - I know, but...
- 你們也被打劫過 - 我知道，可是…
...we didn't get beat up and have all our clothes taken off.
…我們沒有被人打 也沒有被人扒光衣服
It's not even true. The medic threw my clothes away.
不是這樣的 是醫生扔掉了我的衣服
Don't worry about it. Rumours don't mean shit.
別緊張 謠言不重要
We know the truth.
我們知道真相
Right?
對吧？
- Yeah.
- 對
Who knows, this might even get you laid.
誰知道呢，沒準你就泡上了
No, not if she thinks he's gay, Todd. You fucking retard.
不會，如果她以為他是同性戀的話，托德 真笨
- That's really fucking helping me! - I'm just being honest.
- 真的有可能幫到我！ - 我只是實話實說
I was getting back to my old self.
我開始恢復原來的自己
I should have quit, of course...
我應該放棄，當然…
... but you can't just re-programme yourself...
但是人無法改變自己
... what you want, who you are, your purpose in life.
你想要的東西，你是怎樣一個人 你的人生目標
No, I'm just standing around.
不，我只是在這站著而已
No, I'm not!
不，我不是！
- It is what it is. - How about that, huh?
事情就是這樣 知道我的厲害了嗎？
Oh, yeah. Didn't see that, did you?
想見識一下，是嗎？
Think it's best that you just walk away.
你最好趕緊滾開
Well maybe you shouldn't do that.
也許你不該這麼做
What? Huh?
什麼？
Are you looking at me?
你還敢瞪我？
Well, this is my business.
這關我的事
Me? My hardware was fixed now.
我？我的硬體設備都恢復了
I was back and running Kick-Ass version 2.0.
我又回來了 現在是海扁王2.0版
Excuse me. Have you seen this cat?
打擾一下 見過這隻貓嗎？
No? Okay, thank you.
沒有？謝謝
Excuse me, ma'am, have you seen this cat?
打擾一下，女士 見過這隻貓嗎？
I'm sorry, did you see this cat?
打擾了，你見過這隻貓嗎？
No? Okay.
沒有？好的
Oh, great!
哦，太好了！
Here, kitty. Here, Mr Bitey.
過來，貓咪，過來，拜特先生
Come on. No, no, no, no, no.
快點，不，不，不
No, no, no. Mr Bitey, come on.
不，不，不 拜特先生，過來
Back here. Come on, let's get you home. Come on.
回來，開 我帶你回家，快點
Fuck you, Mr Bitey!
我靠，拜特先生！
Oh, God, I'm so sorry, man.
我的天，對不起
You fucking...
你這個…
Thanks, freak.
謝謝，怪物
- Leave him alone. - Fuck off, it's none of your business.
- 放開他 - 滾開，不關你的事
Yes it is.
關我的事
Hey, call 911!
嘿，快去報警！
Hey, there's a dude dressed like a superhero fighting a bunch of guys.
嘿，有個穿成超級英雄的傢伙 在和一群人打架
It's fucking awesome!
真是太帥了！
Leave him alone!
放開他！
Give it up, man. Just walk away.
放棄吧，老兄，快走開
No, never.
不，絕不
What the fuck is wrong with you? You'd rather die for some piece of shit...
你他媽怎麼了？ 你寧願為一個混蛋去死…
...that you don't even fucking know?
…一個陌生人？
You 3 assholes laying into 1 guy while everybody else watches.
你們三個傢伙打一個人 而其他人都在看著
And you wanna know what's wrong with me?!
你想知道我是怎麼回事？
Yeah, I'd rather die. So bring it on!
是的，我寧願死 放馬過來吧！
You're fucking crazy, kid.
你這傢伙瘋了
Thank you.
謝謝
What?!
什麼！
That fucking rocked. Who are you?
太有型了 你是誰？
I'm Kick-Ass.
我是海扁王
Dude, you gotta check this shit out.
老兄，快來看看這個
What is it?
什麼？
And coming up after the hour.
最新新聞
A costume vigilante has become the latest internet phenomenon...
一個穿著制服的見義勇為人士 已經成為最新的網絡紅人…
... after a Hamilton Park resident filmed the man's remarkable intervention...
…漢密爾頓公園附近的一民居民 拍下了這個人士的英勇行為
- This is awesome. - Fuck, yeah!
- 太帥了 - 靠，真的！
Welcome to this special edition of Eye On New York.
歡迎收看本期紐約追蹤的特別節目
How far would you go to help your fellow man?
你會如何幫助別人？
This colourful individual has been all over the news...
這位制服人士已經 成為新聞的焦點…
... after a video of his intervention of street gang violence...
他在街頭對抗暴力的視頻
... became the most watched clip on the internet.
已經成為網上點擊率最高的視頻
You 3 assholes laying into 1 guy...
你們三個傢伙打一個人
My MySpace: 38 friends. Kick-Ass's MySpace:
我的好友：38個 海扁王的好友
... 16,000 and counting.
16,000，而且人數還在增加
This thing was going crazy and I was loving it.
太瘋狂了，我喜歡
And finally, we want to know who is this man.
最後，我們想知道這個人到底是誰
Does anyone have any idea who this wetsuit crusader is?
有沒有人知道內情？
He must be someone's son, someone's brother,
他一定是某個人的兒子 某個人的兄弟
someone's next door neighbour.
某個人的鄰居
Holy shit. What happened?
天啊，發生什麼事了？
This guy happened.
發生什麼事了？ 都是這個傢伙
It's a great day for America, everybody.
這是美國一個重要的日子，所有人
Everybody's favourite superhero right now. Kick-Ass, right?
所有人的超級英雄 海扁王，對嗎？
Yeah!
對
I like Kick-Ass. His costume is crappy.
我喜歡海扁王 儘管他的制服很蹩腳
He looks like a transvestite...
他看起來就像一個易裝癖者
You know what? Everyone likes Kick-Ass.
知道嗎？所有人都喜歡海扁王
Did you see the clip? He was actually pretty good.
你看過視頻嗎？ 他很不錯
Good at getting his ass kicked.
善於被人海扁
He should call himself Ass-Kick instead.
他應該稱自己為被扁王
That doesn't even make sense.
這樣說不通
That guy's gonna end up dead, that's what I think.
這個傢伙一定會死，這是我的看法
Are you serious? The guy owns.
你說真的嗎？這個傢伙很厲害
I'd e-mail his site if I had a problem worth fixing.
如果我有問題需要解決 我也會問給他發郵件
I got 100 guys can fix a problem, you'd hire some putz in pantyhose?
我會派一百個人幫你解決問題 你用不著這個傻瓜
I wouldn't wanna get in the way of your 'business' where I'm not wanted.
我不想打擾你做你的正事
I know you have mistaken me for Kick-Ass, but I am not Kick-Ass.
我知道你們以為我是海扁王 但是我不是
So you don't actually read comics?
所以你不看漫畫嗎？
Ljust started.
剛剛開始看
I got recommended some like Scott Pilgrim and Shojo Beat, that kinda thing.
有人推薦我看歪小子斯科特和少女漫畫之類的
I'm not really into the whole superhero thing, though.
我不大喜歡超級英雄那種漫畫
So I guess you're not gonna line up forthat new Kick-Ass comic, then?
那麼我猜你也不會喜歡 最新的海扁王漫畫？
I guess not. But I was seriously thinking of mailing his site.
我想不會，可是我很認真地 想過給他發郵件
I mean, I could really use some help from a guy like that right now.
我是說，我現在正需要那樣的人幫忙
Help? Really? What with?
幫忙？真的？怎麼幫？
You know I volunteer at the Needle Exchange?
你知道我是針具交換的志願者
No, I didn't.
不，我不知道
Well, there's this one guy, Rasul. I felt so sorry for him and...
有個傢伙，叫拉蘇爾 我很遺憾
...the more I found out about his upbringing and stuff, ljust...
我越瞭解他，我就越…
Wow, that's weird. I'm usually the one playing therapist.
太古怪了，通常是我扮演醫生的角色
Can I make a confession?
我能懺悔嗎？
Ever since I was little I've always wanted a friend...
自從很小的時候 我就想有一個朋友…
...like you.
…像你一樣的朋友
Is it okay to say that? That's not homophobic, is it?
這樣說沒事吧？ 不算反同性戀，對吧？
I mean, I don't think you're all the same or anything.
我的意思是，你對我來說很特別
Of course not, no.
當然不算了
Thank you.
謝謝
I don't know if I was everything Katie dreamed her gay BFF would be...
我不知道我是不是凱蒂 夢想的一輩子的同性戀好朋友
... but I tried my best.
可是我會盡力去做
More importantly, I talked her into mailing Kick-Ass.
更重要的是 我以海扁王的名義跟她聊過天
Long story short, this particular lame duck of hers...
長話短說，她的所謂投機想法
... turned out to be more of a lame cobra.
其實也沒什麼
She didn't want the money back she'd given him...
他不想要回給他的錢
... or an apology for the black eye he'd given her.
也不想他為他的無禮而道歉
She just wanted him to get that they were through and leave her alone.
他只是想告訴他，他們之間的關係結束了 以後別再煩她就行了
And let's be real, no other request could have given me more pleasure.
說實話，這樣的要求讓我很開心
Who the fuck are you supposed to be? The Green Condom?
你以為你是誰？綠色安全套嗎？
You know it ain't Hallowe'en for anotherfew months, kid?
離萬聖節還有還幾個月呢，小傢伙
I'm here to see Rasul.
我來找拉蘇爾
Who the fuck are you?
你到底是誰？
I'm Ki... I'm a friend of Katie's.
我是海…我是凱蒂的朋友
Kids nowadays in theirtights.
現在的小孩都怎麼了
So, which one of you guys is Rasul?
哪一位是拉蘇爾？
I'm Rasul. Can't you tell by my big titties?
我是拉蘇爾 沒看到我豐滿的胸部嗎？
What is this? Trick ortreat or something?
這是什麼？ 特技還是什麼？
Fuck. Now I'm dead.
靠，掛了
I've a message for Rasul about Katie Deauxma.
我來給拉蘇爾帶個關於凱蒂的口信
Katie?
凱蒂？
Oh, you're Rasul?
你是拉蘇爾？
Okay. You gotta stay away from Katie now. It's over.
從現在開始，你別再去打擾凱蒂 一切都結束了
So if you just leave her alone everything will be fine.
如果你照做，就什麼事沒有
What?
什麼？
Yo, kid. Who the hell are you?
小孩，你是誰？
And what is this?
這又是什麼？
I'm Kick-Ass. Look me up.
我是海扁王，看好了
And this is me giving you a message. Leave Katie alone.
我來跟你說，不要再去打擾凱蒂
Or what?
否則呢？
Or... I'll come back...
否則…我會回來…
...and break yourfucking legs.
打斷你的腿
I'm right here now, baby.
我在這兒呢，小朋友
Fuck!
靠！
Hold him.
抓住他
You are so fucking dead, man.
你死定了
Okay, you cunts. Let's see what you can do now.
你們這些討厭鬼 看看你們還能有什麼花樣
Eeny, meeny...
一，二
...miny, mo.
三，四
What the fuck?!
怎麼回事？
Hey, I got one of those.
嘿，我也有一個
Come on.
來啊
So you wanna play.
你也想玩玩
What the fuck?
發生什麼事了？
Oh, dude, that is one gay-looking taser.
老兄，拿著那個泰瑟槍 就像個同性戀
Relax, we're on the same team.
別緊張，我們是夥伴
Hey, get up.
嘿，起來
Now, Hit Girl, we always keep our backs where?
奪命女俠，我們的背部要面向哪堙H
To the wall, Daddy, I know. It won't happen again.
面向牆壁，老爸，我知道 下次不會了
- Nice shot, by the way. - Thank you.
- 好槍法，順便說一句 - 謝謝
Let's go.
我們走吧
Hey, asshole, you can't use the front door now.
嘿，笨蛋，不能走前門
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等
What?
什麼？
Who are you?
你是誰？
Me?
我？
I'm Hit Girl.
我是奪命女俠
And that's: Big Daddy.
那位：神勇老爹
Come on.
快
Come on!
快！
Hit Girl and Big Daddy.
奪命女俠和神勇老爹
They were the real deal.
他們是真材實料
Me?
我？
I was just a stupid dick in a wetsuit.
我只是一個穿著潛水服的蠢貨
What is this? What am I looking at here?
這是什麼？ 我看的是什麼？
It was Sal's phone. They found it in his hand.
這是薩爾的電話 他們在他手上找到的
He must have taken that right before he died.
他死之前一定拿著這個電話
I know this sounds fucked-up, Frankie, but that guy in the picture...
我知道這有點亂，弗蘭克 可是照片堶悸漱H
...I think it's that superhero nut job from the TV.
我想就是電視媦蔽熄W級英雄
Who?
誰？
Kick-Ass?
海扁王？
One guy?
一個人？
Hold on, you're telling me one guy killed 8 of my men tonight?
等等，你是說他一個人單槍匹馬 晚上殺了我八個人？
8 at Sal's place. 4 at that kid Rasul's.
薩爾那邊是八個，還有拉蘇爾那邊有四個
We have no merchandise on the street at all?
我們在街面上是不是沒有貨了？
Right.
對
- One guy? - I think.
- 一個人？ - 我想是
If you're right, we'll look like the biggest pussies in New York.
如果你沒錯的話，我們似乎成了 紐約最好欺負的人
What do you want me to do?
想要我怎麼做？
I want Kick-Ass's fucking head on a stick, and I want it now.
我想要海扁王的人頭，現在就要
I didn't say anything to anyone, I swear.
我沒有跟任何人說任何話，我發誓
Good move, Ass... Kick. Let's keep it that way.
很好，被扁王 我們要保持這樣
You know what this is?
你知道這是什麼嗎？
It's all the cartridge crap that comes out of your gay little taser when you fire it.
這是你開槍時 從你可愛的泰瑟槍堨X來的彈夾
You do know the police could have traced this right back to you if they'd found it?
如果被警察發現了 他們會追蹤到你，知道嗎？
But lucky foryou... I picked it up.
但是幸運的是，我撿到了
Thank you.
謝謝
Let's call it insurance. Makes it easierfor us to take your word.
這是一個保險 這樣我們才會更相信你的話
See, we like you, but we don't trust you.
明白嗎，我們不討厭你 可是我們也不信任你
Don't take it personal. We don't trust anybody.
別太介意 我們不信任任何人
I re-routed your IP address.
我重設了你的IP地址
Finding you was way too easy.
找到你太容易了
Oh, shit. Shit, I hadn't thought. My God.
哦，靠，我沒有想到，我的天
I, I owe you.
我，我欠你一份人情
I'm thinking of shutting my site down anyway.
我倒是在想關掉我的站點
Quitting. I mean, this is... it's fucking insane.
退出，我的意思是，這件事… 太瘋狂了
I'm in way over my head.
我很混亂
It's a shame. You have potential.
很可惜，你有潛質
Your call. But you know we're around if you need us.
好吧，如果你有需要 可以找我們
How do I get a hold of you?
怎麼聯繫你們呢？
You just contact the Mayor's office.
你只要聯繫市長辦公室
He has a special signal he shines in the sky.
他有特殊新號 在天空中發光
In the shape of a giant cock.
形成大公雞的形狀
You need us, put on your website you're on vacation. We'll find you.
如果需要我們，就在網頁上寫你放假了 我們會找到你
Hit Girl, back to headquarters.
奪命女俠，我們回總部
Sweet dreams.
做個美夢
I need you to get rid of Kick-Ass.
我需要你去幹掉海扁王
- Yo. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's up? - What's up?
- 出了什麼事？
Kick-Ass is killing my men, Gigante, that's what's up.
海扁王殺了我的人 吉甘特，就是這件事
My condolences, Frank.
我很遺憾，弗蘭克
But I'm afraid I can't help you on this one.
可是這次我恐怕幫不了你
- Little bit outside my jurisdiction. - Outside your jurisdiction?
- 不在我的職權範圍之內 - 不在你的職權範圍之內？
You're a fucking cop and he's breaking the law.
你是警察，而他犯了法
That's so inside it's ball-deep in your jurisdiction's ass.
怎麼會不在你的職權範圍之內？
Listen to me.
聽我說
The cops pay me to nail the bad guys. You pay me not to.
警察給我錢去揭發壞人 而你給我錢讓我不這麼做
- Everything else is in the grey area. - Fuck you very much. Just do it. Okay.
- 其他事我都不管 - 我靠，照我說的做
Un-fucking-believable.
難以置信
Where's Cody? He's late.
科迪呢？他遲到了
Thank you, Cody. We appreciate your co-operation.
謝謝，科迪 非常感謝你的合作
Let me out now?
可以放我出來了嗎？
I gave you all them names and addresses.
所有的姓名和住址我都給你了
Hey, I won't say nothing to nobody.
我不會對任何人說的
You and your crazy midget friend can go bash whoeveryou want.
你和你的小矮人朋友可以為所欲為了
Hey, come on.
拜託
Hey, I know some very bad people up town. Really nasty individuals.
嘿，我知道富人區一些非常混蛋的人 真的很混蛋
Let me go. Hey, come on.
放我出來，求求你們了
Hey, hey, don't do this. You don't need to do this. Come on.
不要啊，沒有必要，拜託了
Please. Hey.
拜託了
Come on, no, no...
別，別…
No, no, no! Come on, please!
別，別，別！求求你們！
Hey, you're crazy. Please!
你們瘋了，求求你們！
What a douche.
很徹底
You have done self tan before, right?
你以前沒有這樣曬過，是嗎？
Yeah, like, I do it all the time.
事實上，我一直都這麼做
Murder, superheroes breaking into my bedroom.
謀殺，超級英雄闖進了我的生活
My life had turned into some fucked-up dream I couldn't wake up from.
我的生活已經變成一個 無法醒來的噩夢
Even the good parts were totally surreal.
甚至美好的部分也猶如夢幻一般
Oh, hey, I read those old Ditko Spidermans you gave me.
我看了你給我的迪特可蜘蛛人的漫畫
They're actually pretty good.
事實上很好看
Yeah, they are.
對，沒錯
And it's been a whole week since I've heard from Rasul.
拉蘇爾已經有整個禮拜都沒有騷擾我了
That's great.
很好
Once upon a time there were 2 supercops called Daddy and Marcus...
曾經有兩個超級警察 他們叫老爹和馬庫斯
... who were very good at getting bad guys.
他們抓壞人的本領很厲害
Frank D'Amico was the baddest guy of them all...
弗蘭克·達米科是最大的壞人
... and he came up with a plan to get rid of Daddy.
他想出一條惡毒的計策 擺脫老爹
Being framed as a drug dealer was the worst thing that could have happened to Daddy.
難以置信的是，老爹被誣告成為毒販
Prison was not his natural habitat.
他沒有想到會被關入監獄
He was very upset.
他很傷心
With Daddy in prison, his pregnant wife was all alone...
老爹入獄期間 懷有身孕的妻子孤身一人
... and could not cope.
無法面對自己的生活
But all clouds have a silver lining and out of her death...
但是，黑暗中常有一線曙光 她死後
... Mindy was born.
明迪出生了
Marcus became the child's guardian...
馬庫斯成為孩子的監護人
... and Daddy started a plan of his very own.
而老爹開始了他自己的計劃
5 years later he left prison, and he was ready.
五年後他離開監獄 並且準備好了
Now it was time for Mindy to get ready, too.
現在輪到明迪也要準備好了
How did you find me, Marcus?
你是怎麼找到我的，馬庫斯？
One of us is still a cop, remember?
我還是警察，忘了嗎？
Is this how you brainwashed Mindy?
這就是你給明迪洗腦的辦法？
You say brainwashed, I say made it into a game.
你認為是洗腦 我認為是一場遊戲
You call this playing, Damon?
你把這個叫做遊戲，戴蒙？
Vigilante justice. Mass murder. Come on, partner.
見義勇為，大屠殺 別鬧了，夥計
So where is she?
她在哪？
- She's safe. - Can I see her?
- 她很安全 - 我能看看她嗎？
I miss her.
我很想她
I miss you both.
我想你們
I appreciate your concern, but you need to go now.
謝謝你的關心 你得離開這堣F
I should warn you, that asshole Gigante is looking for Kick-Ass.
我要警告你，吉甘特那個混蛋 正在找海扁王
He got something to do with you, Damon?
他跟你有關，是不是？
You started some kind of fucked-up superhero club?
你是不是成立了一個 超級英雄俱樂部？
- Never heard of him. - Okay. Heads up, all right?
- 沒有聽說過這個人 - 好，當心點，知道嗎？
You keep carrying on like you been carrying on,
你一直這麼做下去
it's only a matter of time before Gigante is looking foryou.
吉甘特遲早會找到你
He's been on D'Amico's payroll ever since you passed up the opportunity.
自從你錯過了那次機會 吉甘特就已經被達米科收買了
You know I'm not gonna stop.
你知道我不會停止行動的
Not until D'Amico and his whole damn operation...
直到達米科以及他的計劃
...are burnt to ashes and buried.
全部完蛋
It ain't gonna bring her back, Damon.
這樣也不能讓她起死回生，戴蒙
This is not the life for Mindy.
明迪不該過這樣的生活
You owe that kid a childhood.
你欠孩子一個正常的童年生活
I'll tell you who owes her a childhood.
我告訴你是誰欠孩子一個童年
Frank D'Amico!
弗蘭克·達米科
Holy shit.
我的天
I don't fucking believe it.
真不敢相信
Follow him, round the corner.
跟著他，轉過街角
Not too fast.
別太快
What's with the high-fives?
還擊掌慶祝
I'll give you a motherfucking high-five.
我待會也給你來一個
High-fiving bullshit. Keep going, keep going.
慶祝個鳥 跟上，跟上
Not too close.
別太近
He's going in the alley.
他往巷子堥咫F
Okay, when I tell you, stop the car. Ready?
好的，聽我命令停車，準備好了嗎？
Hey, Kick-Ass.
嘿，海扁王
How you doing?
你好嗎？
Kill my men, huh? Take my fucking coke!
殺我的人 拿我的貨！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, boss. What are you doing?
老闆，快停下
Boss, come on, we gotta go, baby.
老闆，快，我們快走
- Fucking scumbag! - Come on, let's go.
- 沒用的傢伙！ - 快，我們走
Boss, come on, he's had enough.
老闆，快走，夠了
Come on, Frank, he's had enough. Come on.
快，弗蘭克，夠了，快走
What the fuck are you looking at? Huh?
你在看什麼呢？
Come on, come on. Come on, let's go. We gotta go.
快點，快點，快點，我們走 我們快走
Fuck. Shit. Damn.
靠，媽的
Come on, come on, get in.
快，快，上車
He was so young. No one should have to die that way.
他還這麼年輕 誰知道就這麼死了
I mean, I just can't believe he's dead, that's all.
我真的不敢相信他已經死了
I know. But, Katie,
我明白，可是，凱蒂
guys like Rasul, they get mixed up in stuff...
像拉蘇爾那樣的人 他們的生活本來就是一團糟
No, I know, I know. But what if it was my fault?
我知道，我知道 但萬一他的死是我造成的呢？
What if Kick-Ass did it?
萬一是海扁王干的呢？
I mean, I feel like I should call the cops or something.
我覺得應該打電話報警什麼的
What? You're talking crazy.
什麼？別瞎說了
There's no way. He probably didn't even read your e-mail yet.
不可能的，他沒準都沒看到你的郵件
- Yeah. - You've got nothing to worry about.
- 是嗎? - 沒什麼好擔心的
I'm so glad you're here.
你能來這我很開心
I was such a mess.
我現在一團糟
That's okay.
沒事的
- No problem. - You're the best.
- 沒事的 - 你太好了
I hope it's okay to say this, but... It so sucks that you're gay.
希望你不要介意 很可惜你是個同性戀
I don't fucking believe this.
真不敢相信
What kind of children's enter-fucking-tainer is that?
這群小鬼有什麼不好玩?
What kind of kid has a... A Spider-Man party, sure, but a fucking Kick-Ass party?
不能搞個蜘蛛俠派對嗎？ 搞什麼海扁王派對
What, are they selling paper plates and napkins down at the store now?
樓下賣紙盤和餐巾紙的也都瘋了
Frank, you're scaring me. You're losing it.
弗蘭克，你嚇到我 你太激動了
Since when did you start getting your hands dirty again? And in public!
你什麼時候又開始親自動手了？ 還在光天化日之下
Since when I ask you fucks to deliver me Kick-Ass,
自從海扁王這傢伙開始煩我的時候
- and you don't deliver, that's when. - Give me a break. It's been a week.
- 而你到現在還沒有搞定他 - 讓我喘口氣行不行？都已經一個禮拜了
We e-mailed him. We got half the crew out doing petty crimes as bait.
我們給他寫郵件 找了一半手下惹事當誘餌
We're busting our asses here.
我們都沒閒著
What the hell are you doing?
你要幹嘛？
You're back on the powder now, as well?
你又開始繼續嗑藥了？
"Mommy, I want a Kick-Ass party." Dumb little fucks.
媽媽，我想參加海扁王派對 媽的混蛋
- I know a way you can get him. - Shit.
- 我知道怎樣才能抓到他 - 靠
Chris, how long you been there?
克奡窗A你什麼時候來的？
What the hell are you doing? Get the hell out.
你來幹什麼？ 還不快點出去
Do you want to hear it or not?
你想不想聽？
- Hear what? - Okay, look,
- 聽什麼？ - 是這樣
you're a superhero and you're lonely, but you can't trust anyone
你是一個超級英雄，但是你很孤獨 你不能相信任何人
'cause either they'll expose your secret identity...
因為別人可能會洩露你的身份
Comic books this kid reads all fucking day long.
漫畫書，整天就知道看漫畫書
The point is there's only one way a superhero can trust a stranger.
重點是，我有一個辦法 可以讓超級英雄信任一個陌生人
And I can be that stranger. You just gotta give me a chance.
我可以做那個陌生人 只要你給我一個機會
I know I can do it. I just need a few things.
我可以做得到 只是需要一些道具
Like what?
比如說？
I need these things.
我需要這些東西
What, are you fucking kidding me? What the hell is this?
什麼，你在開什麼玩笑？ 這些是什麼？
It's everything I need.
這就是我所需要的所有東西
And you might have to screw someone over, like Louie, or something.
還有你需要犧牲一個人 路易或是別人
- Louie? Hey, Chris. - Or somebody. It doesn't have to be Louie.
- 路易？ 嘿，克奡 - 其他人也行，不一定非得是路易
- Tony! - Tony.
- 托尼！ - 托尼？
- Tony? - I hate Tony.
- 我討厭托尼
Yeah, fuck Tony. He's a scumbag.
對，托尼是個廢物
I swear, Dad, if you let me do this, it's gonna work.
我發誓，老爸 如果你給我機會，一定可以
Tony.
托尼
Tony Romita, one of America's most-wanted crime kingpins,
托尼·羅密塔 被通緝的美國最大犯罪集團的主腦之一
was arrested in Queens today
今天在皇后區被捕
after a 911 call from someone claiming to be a superhero...
有人報警，自稱為超級英雄
So, how are things going with Katie?
你和凱蒂怎麼樣了？
Just peachy.
還行吧
We had a sleepover and spent the whole night
在她家過夜了
watching the entire Ugly Betty box set and did pedicures.
整晚都在看《醜女貝蒂》專輯 還修了趾甲
I'm telling you, the longer you wait, the worse it's gonna get.
我告訴你，等得越久，事情就越難辦
I know. I was gonna tell her. It's just, she seems so happy.
我知道，我本打算告訴她 只是她看起來很開心
- I don't know when's the right time. - Now's your chance.
- 我不知道什麼時候說合適 - 現在就是好機會
- She didn't see that, did she? - Hey, guys.
- 她還不知道，是吧？ - 大家好
- Hi! - Hi, sweetie.
- 嗨！ - 嗨，寶貝
Did you watch the TV? The new superhero guy?
你們看電視了嗎？ 新的超級英雄？真酷
- How cool is that? - What?
- 有多酷？ - 什麼？
- Hey, look. - Could you turn it up, please?
- 看 - 聲音能不能開大一點？
- Check this out. - ...dressed as Kick-Ass.
- 看這個 - 類似於海扁王的打扮
But it seems that far from being put off, this individual, who calls himself Red Mist,
但是看起來毫不遜色 這位，自稱為紅色迷霧
has decided to take crime-fighting to a new level,
已經決定將打擊犯罪的行動提升到新的高度
as his actions last night proved. Red Mist, how do you see it?
他昨晚的行動證明了這一點
Well, I guess folks have just had enough of living in fear, you know,
我想人們已經受夠了擔驚受怕的日子
and Kick-Ass really proved that one individual can make a difference.
海扁王已經證明 一個人的力量也可以有所作為
So if anyone out there needs help, I'll be fighting crime 25/8.
所以，如果有人需要幫助 我會第一時間趕到犯罪現場
And I'm just one click away. Redmist. org.
點擊我的網站：RedMist.org
Can we turn that off now? What's so special about that guy?
能不能關掉電視？ 他有什麼特別？
He caught, like, a drug dealer, some most-wanted guy.
他好像抓住了一個大毒梟
You saw him bringing out like a ton of stuff.
他在現場繳獲無數毒品
That's pretty cool.
真酷
He's got a way better costume than Kick-Ass, too.
是的，造型也比海扁王好點
- He's got a cape. - Yeah.
- 他有一個披風 - 對
- Capes rock. - Yeah, I'm kind of feeling the cape.
- 還是披風帥 - 沒錯，我都能感覺到那件披風
He looks good.
看起來不錯
What, better than Kick-Ass?
什麼，比海扁王酷?
I mean, they're both kind of hot. I just think Red Mist has a better body.
我是說，他們都很性感 我只是覺得紅色迷霧的身材要好一點
Don't you think, Dave?
你怎麼看，戴夫？
Yeah, Dave, what do you think?
是啊，戴夫你怎麼看？
Is he the kind of guy you'd go for, with all that leather?
這不就是你喜歡的類型嗎？ 全身皮裝
No, Marty. No, he's not really my type.
不，我不喜歡 他不是我喜歡的型
Kick-Ass!
海扁王！
Red Mist.
紅色迷霧
Shit! Fuck me, that kind of hurt.
靠！好痛啊！
- Are you okay? - Yeah, no, I'm cool.
- 沒事吧？ - 我沒事
I can't believe you're here, man. Like, you're my hero.
真不敢相信你就在眼前 你是我的偶像
You inspired me. No Kick-Ass, no Red Mist.
是你給了我靈感 沒有海扁王，就沒有紅色迷霧
- Seriously. - Wow.
真的
- Hey, really? - Straight up. And listen, if you...
- 真的嗎？ - 我直說吧，如果你
I don't know, if you wanted me to be your sidekick or something...
我不知道合不合適 如果我可以成為你的拍檔的話
You wanna be my sidekick?
你想成為我的拍檔？
Yeah, man! You and me together, we would own!
是的！ 我們聯手，一定會成功
You wanna go fight some crime?
你想打擊犯罪嗎？
What you mean, like, right now?
你是說現在？
Yeah, man, come on. I got something I wanna show you.
是的，來，我給你看樣東西
I mean, like, to be honest with you,
我想…老實說
I only ever fight crime between like 9:00 and 2:00, weekdays.
我只在9點到2點之間行動，工作日
So I'm gonna need to get back pretty soon.
所以我得很快就回去了
Sweet!
太帥了！
- Is that yours? - Meet the Mist Mobile.
- 是你的嗎？ - 見識一下迷霧跑車
SatNav. Got my iPhone, so I can check the websites
導航系統連接了我的iPhone 所以我兜風時可以瀏覽網頁
for emergencies when I'm driving around.
看看有沒有緊急情況
Got a little bit of mood lighting right there.
這是心情燈光
Rearview camera, no big deal.
後視攝像頭，沒什麼大不了的
Check this, you're gonna fucking love this.
看看這個，你一定會喜歡的
The mist.
迷霧
Hey.
嘿
That's right, we're superheroes. You love us.
超級英雄就是這麼受歡迎
- Smoke? - No.
- 抽煙嗎？ - 不了
I feel a little weed takes the edge off things when I'm on patrol, you know?
巡邏的時候抽一根有助於放鬆心情
Going up against a crowd can get kind of scary, don't you think?
在人群當中還真有點受寵若驚 你不覺得嗎？
Something wrong?
怎麼了？
Yeah. You're so not how I expected.
你跟我想像中不太一樣
I got this e-mail from this chick.
我收到了一個小妞的郵件
She said this guy's been following her home from work.
她說這個傢伙 在她下班回家時跟蹤她
I got her address and stuff. You wanna check it out?
我有她的地址 你想去看看怎麼回事嗎？
- Sure, why not? - Cool.
- 當然，為什麼不去？ - 好的
So we're sitting there totally naked, right?
我們都脫光了衣服，對不對？
I told her, "Sit on my lap, we'll talk about the first thing that comes up."
我跟她說，坐在我的大腿上 把腦子媟Q到的第一件事說出來
- Yeah? - Just got the text. He's on his way.
- 怎麼樣？ - 剛收到風，他在路上了
He did very good.
很好
- Don't kill him till I get there. - Right.
- 別急著殺他，等我過去 - 好的
Looks like reading all them comics paid off, huh?
看那麼多漫畫書還是有用的，是吧？
Your boy did good, Frankie.
你兒子這次幹得不錯，弗蘭克
He's his father's son.
我的兒子嘛
I forgot.
差點忘了
What the fuck?
怎麼回事？
Shit.
靠
- Hey, what are you doing? - There are people in there.
- 嘿！你要幹嘛？ - 堶惘酗H！
Yeah. Shouldn't we call the fire...
我們是不是該報警…
Shit!
靠！
- Shit. Fuck. - Red Mist!
紅色迷霧！
Red Mist! Red Mist!
紅色迷霧！紅色迷霧！
Hey. Hey, man, can you hear me? Hey.
嘿，你在哪啊？
Jesus Christ!
我的天！
Red Mist! Red Mist!
紅色迷霧！紅色迷霧！
Where the fuck are you?
你到底在哪？
We gotta get the hell out of here. Dude, move your fucking ass!
我們得離開這！ 快跑！
Holy shit!
靠！
- Did you see those bodies? - Yeah, man.
- 你看到那些屍體了嗎？ - 看到了
- Why'd you save the teddy? - What?
- 為什麼要救這只熊？ - 什麼？
I don't know, man. Come on.
我不知道，我們快走
Come.
進來
What the hell are you doing, Frank?
你到底想幹嘛，弗蘭克？
You know I can't be here. What if somebody saw...
你知道我不能來這 如果被人看到…
That motherfucker Kick-Ass burnt down my warehouse
海扁王那個小雜種 放火燒了我的倉庫
and killed my men, Gigante.
還殺了我的人，吉甘特
Wait, wait, wait. Slow down. Kick-Ass?
等等，說什麼，海扁王？
- Are you sure? - You gotta help me, Vic.
- 你確定？ - 你得幫我，維克
My son was there, and he's still missing.
我兒子也在堶 現在還沒找到
They're all dead! Everybody in the warehouse is dead.
他們都死了！ 倉庫堜狾釭漱H都死了！
Put the gun down, Vic. It's Chris.
把槍放下，維克，他是克奡窗I
Chris is Red Mist?
克奡絕N是紅色迷霧?
It's not Red Mist you gotta worry about. It's Kick-Ass.
別管紅色迷霧 要擔心的是海扁王！
No, no, no, it's not. Kick-Ass is just some geek, Dad.
不，不，不，不是這樣 海扁王只是一個怪人，老爸
You don't have to worry about him. You need to watch this.
你不必擔心他 看看這個！
- Why, what does it do? - Are you fucking kidding me?
- 為什麼？這是什麼？ - 不是在開玩笑吧？
- What? - God damn it, just sit down.
- 什麼？ - 真離譜，你們坐下
What are you doing? What the hell is that thing?
你要幹什麼？ 那是什麼玩意？
You bought this to spy on the nanny when I was a kid. Don't you remember?
這是我小時候你買來監視保姆的 還記得嗎？
- What, and you put it in the warehouse? - Yeah, I thought it'd be cool
- 怎麼？你把它放到倉庫了? - 是的，我覺得
to put the unmasking of Kick-Ass on the Internet, okay?
把海扁王的素顏照 放到網上一定會很酷，是吧？
Watch.
看吧
I told her, "Sit on my lap, we'll talk about the first thing that comes up."
我跟她說，坐在我的大腿上 把腦子媟Q到的第一件事說出來
- Yeah? - Just got the text. He's on his way.
- 怎麼樣？ - 剛收到風，他在路上了
He did very good.
很好
- Don't kill him till I get there. - Right.
- 別急著殺他，等我過去 - 好的
Who the hell is this guy?
這個人是誰？
I don't know, Dad.
我不知道，老爸
But Kick-Ass told me we're not the only superheroes in town.
但是海扁王跟我說過 紐約還有別的超級英雄
Maybe he knows who this guy is.
也許他知道這個人是誰
I want this place locked down.
我要把這兒封鎖起來
Nobody comes in, nobody goes out.
別讓人進來，也別讓人出去
Not until somebody finds this cocksucker
一定要找到這個混蛋
and pulls his fucking lungs out through his ass.
打他個落花流水
Listen, they're on to you.
聽著，他們找上你了？
Do you hear me? They're on to you.
聽見了嗎？他們找上你了
I thought they were looking for Kick-Ass.
我還以為他們在找海扁王
Not anymore. Gigante just put on a little movie-show for us.
不再是了 吉甘特剛給我們放了一段視頻
Different superhero in a warehouse, killing a whole bunch of D'Amico's guys.
又一個超級英雄 在倉庫媟F掉了一幫達米科的人
I'm gonna take a wild guess that was you.
我猜那個就是你吧?
- I killed all the cameras. - Apparently not.
- 我把所有的攝像頭都砸了 - 顯然並非如此
Look, bro, you need to get ghost. Hide yourself quick.
聽著，兄弟 你得馬上消失，快躲起來
Appreciate it.
非常感謝
Mindy,
明迪
no more homework, baby doll.
別做作業了，寶貝
It's time for Frank D'Amico to go bye-bye.
是時候跟弗蘭克·達米科說再見了
X- Men, the Fantastic Four, right now, I envy the crap out of them.
X戰警，神奇四俠 我很羨慕他們
Everything was out of control. I didn't know what the hell to do.
一切都失控了 我不知道該怎麼做
You okay, buddy? You look tired. Early night tonight, maybe?
你還好嗎，戴夫？你看上去很累 要不今晚早點睡覺?
And there was no one I could talk to about it.
我也找不到人可以傾訴這件事
Dave? Hello?
戴夫？喂？
Yeah, you bet I will.
嗯，我會的
I'd never felt more alone.
我從未感到如此孤獨
I'd always dreamed of being a superhero, but this was a nightmare.
我一直夢想著成為超級英雄 但這一切簡直是個惡夢
It was time to stop wearing this stupid costume.
是時候脫下這身愚蠢的衣服了
But there was one last thing I needed it for.
但我還要穿著它做最後一件事
What's the difference between Spider-Man and Peter Parker?
蜘蛛俠跟彼得·帕克有什麼區別？
Spider-Man gets the girl.
蜘蛛俠有美女相伴
Hey, I'm Kick-Ass.
嘿，我是海扁王！
I'm Kick-Ass. You mail me?
我是海扁王 我收到你的郵件
Wait...
等等
Fuck! Fuck!
靠！靠！
Fucking freak in a mask! Get out of my house!
戴面具的死變態 快從我家滾出去
I'm not gonna hurt you, all right?
我不會傷害你的
No, no, no! It's me, it's me!
不，不，是我，是我
All right? I was only trying to surprise you. I'm...
我只是想給你個驚喜
- Dave? What the fuck are you doing? - I'm sorry.
- 戴夫？ 你到底想幹嘛？ - 對不起
- Why are you dressed as Kick-Ass? - Because I am Kick-Ass.
- 你為什麼要穿成海扁王的樣子？ - 因為我就是海扁王
- What are you talking about? - And I'm also not gay.
- 你胡說什麼？ - 我也不是同性戀
- Fuck! - And I'm an idiot and a shit friend.
- 靠！ - 我知道我一直都很傻，不是一個稱職的朋友
I lied to you, I know.
我欺騙了你，我知道
- Oh, my God. - I know. If it makes you feel any better,
- 我的天 - 我知道，如果這能讓你感覺好一些
I don't think you can hate me any more right now than I hate myself.
你一定恨死我了 我也恨我自己
Please, I'm...
拜託，我…
Look, I'm really, really sorry.
聽著，我真的真的很抱歉
I've never met anyone who's as beautiful and as kind and lovely as you.
我從沒見過像你這樣漂亮、善良 可愛的人
You deserve better.
你應該跟更好的人在一起
- Dave. - Yes?
- 戴夫 - 嗯？
My mom has the burglar alarm on downstairs,
我媽媽在樓下裝防盜警鈴
so you should probably use the window.
也許你應該從窗戶出去
Or...
或者
Or you could just stay.
你可以留下來
Stay?
留下來？
What, like when we have a sleepover?
像上次那樣通宵看電視？
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
抱歉，我並不想嚇你
We gotta get over it,
我們得到上面去
on top of it, and then into it, right in the middle of it.
再從正中間下去
Daddy, I think I found one.
老爸，我找到了
It's perfect, and they can deliver it in three days.
太完美了，他們能在三天內送過來
It's 300,000 bucks.
可是要30萬美元
Can you think of anything else you'd rather spend it on?
你還能想到把錢花在別的地方嗎？
Oh, my gosh!
天啊！
- That is cool. - Yeah.
- 真酷！ - 沒錯
Add to shopping cart.
加入購物車
Okay.
好的
Out of Kick-Ass and Red Mist, who do you think would win in a fight?
海扁王跟紅色迷霧對打 你覺得誰會贏？
Why are they fighting? That seems stupid.
他們為什麼要打？ 那樣太傻了
- What do you think? - I don't know, but I think Kick-Ass is cuter.
- 你覺得呢 - 不知道，但我覺得海扁王更可愛一點
Really?
真的？
I, for one, would definitely fuck his brains out if I got the chance.
如果我有機會 一定把他打個稀巴爛
You would?
你會嗎?
Definitely.
當然
Do you feel like checking out that new Kate Hudson movie
你想不想去看凱特·哈里森的新片？
where she's like a shoe designer, can't get a guy?
就是她演鞋子設計師的那部
- I think we could make the next showing. - Hell, yeah.
- 我覺得能趕上下一場 - 好啊
I guess we're not invited.
貌似沒有請我們
All right. You know what? Come here.
好的，知道嗎，過來
I'm going to convert you to a comics reader right now.
我來給你點一道大餐
Suddenly, I understood why superheroes only existed in comic books.
忽然之間，我明白了 為什麼超級英雄只在漫畫埵s在
I got why people didn't risk their lives for strangers.
我明白了為什麼人們不願為陌生人冒險
Because for the first time in my life,
因為，我人生中第一次
I had something worth living for,
有了值得活下去的東西
something to lose.
害怕失去的東西
Katie worried about me getting hurt,
凱蒂擔心我會受傷
so I promised her my Kick-Ass days were over.
所以我保證再也不當海扁王了
And the truth was I hardly missed it at all.
事實上我一點也不懷念那段日子
I hadn't even checked the website for, like, a week.
我已經有一個星期 沒有上那個網頁了
Okay, I'm off then.
好的，我出去了
- No Katie tonight? - Tomorrow.
- 今晚不陪凱蒂? - 明天
Wednesdays, she's got one of those volunteer things.
她週三要當志願者
You seem like a different guy, you know that?
你簡直變了一個人，知道嗎？
Your mom would have been so happy to see you out of your shell like this.
看到你變成這樣 你媽媽一定會很開心
Have a good night.
晚安
- Hey, baby. - Hey, what's going on?
- 嘿，寶貝 - 嘿，還好嗎？
I gotta do a Kick-Ass thing.
我要再當一次海扁王
What? I thought you were done with that.
什麼？你不是說已經退出了嗎？
This is the last time. I totally swear.
這是最後一次，我發誓
I worry about you.
我很擔心你
Well, I wish you wouldn't worry.
你別擔心
I can't help it. I do because I...
我無法控制自己 真的，因為我…
I care about you a lot.
我很在乎你
I care about you a lot, too.
我也是
This better be pretty serious, dude,
最好是有要緊事要說，老兄
'cause I promised my girlfriend that I'm done with all this shit.
因為我向我女朋友保證不幹這行了
How about both of us being dead? Is that serious enough for you?
我們都快死了？這算不算要緊事？
Dead? How?
會死？為什麼？
It turns out those dead guys from the warehouse
倉庫堥漕レ澈
had some bad motherfuckers for friends, and they think we did that shit.
他們的混蛋朋友 認為是我們幹的
There's a price on our heads, man.
他們正在懸賞我們的人頭
A price on our heads? What is this, the Wild West?
懸賞我們的人頭？ 這是哪？西部荒野嗎？
I'm not messing with you, dude. They found out where I lived.
我是說真的，老兄！ 他們找到了我住的地方
They trashed my place. I'm fucking screwed.
他們砸了我的家！我完了！
- And you're gonna be next, okay? - What?
- 下一個就是你，明白嗎？ - 什麼？
Shit.
靠
What do we do?
我們怎麼辦？
Remember you mentioned that there are other superheroes?
記得你說過還有別的超級英雄
Yeah?
是的
Well, do you think they can help us?
他們能幫幫我們嗎？
Hot chocolate, extra marshmallows.
熱巧克力，多加了棉花糖
Man, that looks even cooler than it did in the picture.
比照片上還要酷
Child, you know, that's because in the picture, it didn't have Gatling guns.
孩子 這是因為照片堨i沒有格林機槍
Nice job.
漂亮
I'm gonna take mine to bed, okay?
我要去睡了
Okay, baby doll. Sleep tight.
好的，寶貝 睡個好覺
Thanks. Kick-Ass?
謝謝，海扁王？
You go get dressed. I'll tell him to meet us at Safe House B.
你去穿好衣服 我告訴他去B號安全地
We'll have our hot chocolate when we get back.
回來再喝了
- Okay, Daddy. - Come on.
- 好的，老爸 - 快
- Do you know where that is? - No, but I'll just put it in the GPS.
- 知道那是哪嗎？ - 不知道，我來輸進GPS
- It's what it's for. - All right, let's go.
好了，走
Shit.
靠
Okay, okay, okay.
好的，好的
Well, here you are and Red Mist, too.
你來了，還有紅色迷霧
- Pleasure to meet you. - Good to meet you, sir.
- 很高興見到你 - 我也是，先生
Please, come in.
請進
After you.
你先
Hit Girl, manners, honey.
奪命女俠，要有禮貌，寶貝
Hi, I'm Hit Girl.
嗨，我是奪命女俠
No!
不！
Your ass is mine! Come on.
跟我走，快點
No, he's with me. He's okay.
他是我這邊的，別抓他
Shut the fuck up, kid. Your daddy's the boss. You go home.
閉嘴，孩子，你爸說了算！ 你趕快回家
Are you shitting me? No, he's fine. He's with me.
你在說什麼？別抓他 他是我這邊的
- Let him go. - Get out of here. Get the fuck out of here.
- 放他走 - 滾出去，快給我滾出去
Hot damn. I always wanted one of these.
我的天，我一直想有這麼一個東西
- You're seriously gonna take that? - Yes.
- 你真的要拿走? - 是的
Come on, sweet cheeks.
快走吧
If you don't get your wannabe superhero ass in the car...
如果你不快點上車
- That's funny. - ...you're gonna have a lot of trouble
你就會有麻煩了
- on your hands. - That's really funny. You're so fired.
你有種，很快就讓你滾蛋
- Kick-Ass... - Get him out of here. Get him out of here.
- 海扁王 - 帶他離開，帶他離開
- Get him in the van. - Let go of me. Put me down.
- 讓他上車 - 放開我
Kick-Ass, I'm sorry!
海扁王，對不起
- Get in the car. - Get in there!
- 進去 - 上車
You better fire this asshole.
你最好炒了這個混蛋！
Ignore him...
別管他
A bazooka?
火箭筒？
- Okay. - We had a deal, Dad.
- 好的 - 我們說好的，老爸
We had a fucking deal that I would get you the guy who did it,
我幫你抓到罪魁禍首
and all I'm asking is you let Kick-Ass go. He didn't do anything wrong.
你答應我放了海扁王！ 他什麼也沒有做過
Chris, you got to look at this from my point of view. Okay?
克奡窗A你要從我的角度看事情，好嗎？
I gotta send a public service message to the people out there
我要向公眾傳遞一個信息
that being a superhero is bad for your health.
當超級英雄是有害健康的
And the Big motherfucker? Nobody knows who he is.
至於那個大混蛋，沒人知道他是誰
- Yeah, but that's not fair! - Yeah, life's not fair, kid. Get over it.
- 是的，但這不公平！ - 人生本來就就是不公平的，接受吧
What are you gonna do to them?
你要怎樣對付他們？
You really wanna be a part of my business?
你真的想接我的班，是吧?
Yeah.
是的
Then sit down, shut up and watch.
那就坐下，別說話，好好看著
Frank, we're ready. Enjoy the show.
弗蘭克，我們準備好了 欣賞演出吧
- Are you controlling this right now? - I sure am.
- 你打算這樣來解決? - 顯然我說了算
Big Brother, watch and learn.
看的時候學著點
Welcome back. Breaking News.
歡迎回來，突發新聞
A worldwide web broadcast of the New York superhero
紐約的超級英雄，自稱為海扁王的
who calls himself Kick-Ass is about to be shown live.
即將在網上進行 一場現場直播的表演
Rumors have it that this will be Kick-Ass's farewell appearance,
有謠言說這將是海扁王的最後一次露面
that he will announce his retirement from crime fighting.
他將宣佈結束打擊犯罪的生涯
But as word of mouth continues to spread,
民眾議論紛紛
Internet providers are predicting that
網絡供應商預測
it could be one of the most widely-viewed live events in web history.
這將是網絡史上最受關注的現場直播
Wait, where's Dave?
戴夫去哪了？
- Holy shit. Have you guys noticed... - He's with Katie.
- 你們有沒注意到… - 他跟凱蒂在一起
- Obviously. - ...come to a standstill to watch.
很顯然
Why else would I be here?
要不然我怎麼會在這
There's no idea as to who is behind the broadcast of this show,
雖然還不知道是誰策劃了這場表演
but we could see widespread server crashes...
但是我們得知服務器已經嚴重擁堵
Dave, why didn't you tell me this is what you were doing?
戴夫，為什麼不告訴我你要這麼做
You're on the news. Call me.
你上電視了，記得給我回電話
We go now over live to the countdown clock as we are moments away.
直播倒計時，我們很快就會大開眼界了
Show time.
表演開始
Hello, boys and girls.
大家好
Now, this...
還有…
Well, you know who this guy is.
你們都很熟悉了
And this guy here is Big Daddy.
還有…這位是神勇老爹
And these are my friends.
還有我的朋友
Come on in, guys, say hello.
過來打個招呼
Yeah, yeah, there they are. Hello, hello.
來了，大家好
Now Big Daddy and Kick-Ass are gonna help us
現在神勇老爹和海扁王 會幫助你們認識到
show you why being a hero is a bad idea.
為什麼想做超級英雄是一個錯誤的想法
You know what a silent "K" is?
知道什麼是不發音的K嗎？
That's when "K" is at the beginning of the word,
就是K打頭的單詞 那個K通常不發音
but you don't pronounce it. Like in the word "Knuckleduster."
正如knuckle duster(關節式手套)這個詞一樣
Show them what a knuckleduster can do, guy.
讓他們看看關節式手套的厲害
That must have hurt! Let's see that again from the other side.
一定很痛 另一邊也來一下
Go on. Yeah, I think it did.
繼續，效果不錯
Now in France, they say the word "stick" like this, baston.
法國人是這麼說 "棍"這個單詞 Ba-ton
We got some of Kick-Ass's bastons.
我們還有海扁王的棍子
We're gonna show you what they can do. Go ahead, boys.
給你們看看能這個棍子的用途 動手
In America, we say "stick" like this. Baseball bat.
在美國，我們怎麼稱呼棍子呢 棒球棍
Which is very good for hitting knees and stomachs.
可以打膝蓋和胃部
It's also good for hitting balls.
打這堣]很好用
Know what else we do? We don't do them individually.
還有，我們不喜歡單打獨鬥
We do them all together. Gentlemen, please.
我們喜歡一起上 先生們請吧
Yeah. This looks very painful.
似乎很痛苦啊
Due to the distressing nature of the images, we are unable to broadcast the events
由於畫面太過血腥 我們現在不能在網上進行現場直播了
currently streaming live on the Internet.
在網上進行現場直播了
- Fuck. - No. No, no, no.
不，不
Despite initial speculation that this may be some kind of hoax or publicity stunt,
之前誤導大家的信息說明 這可能是場騙局或是噱頭
it is now clear that the hostages are in genuine danger,
現在可以看到人質的處境很危險
that all signs point to the intention to stage a live execution in the next few minutes.
所有的跡象表明 很快將會出人命
Even with my metal plates and my fucked-up nerve endings,
即使我身體有金屬板 神經末梢也不敏感
I got to tell you, that hurt.
但我得告訴你們，真的很痛
Yes, the silent killer.
對，這就是沉默的殺手
But not half as much as the idea of leaving everything behind.
但最更讓我痛苦的是 我要和所有的一切說再見了
Katie,
凱蒂
my dad,
老爸
Todd and Marty.
托德和馬蒂
And all the things I'd never do, like learn to drive,
以及所有我還沒有來得及做的事情 比如學開車
or see what me and Katie's kids would look like
還有看看我和凱蒂的孩子長得怎麼樣
or find out what happened on Lost.
我還沒看到《迷失》的結局
And if you're reassuring yourself
如果你以為
that I'm gonna make it through this since I'm talking to you now,
我還在說話，我一定能挺過去
quit being such a smartass.
別太天真了
Hell, dude, you never seen Sin City, Sunset Blvd., American Beauty?
夥計，你沒看過《罪惡之城》？ 《日落大道》，《美國麗人》?
And this, for all you cavemen out there,
還有這個 給你們準備的
is fire.
火
No.
不
I know.
我知道
Fire. Fire is good.
火，火是好東西
Fire is our friend.
火是我們的朋友
Gentlemen,
先生們
time to die.
死期到了
What the...
怎麼回…
What the fuck just happened? Hey, hey. Somebody find the lights.
剛才怎麼回事？ 快找打火機
Hello!
你好！
Jesus Christ.
我的上帝
Bobby? Bobby?
鮑比？鮑比？
Get the lighter!
打火機
It's on the floor right over there. Find the lighter.
就在地上 快去拿打火機
I got it.
我拿到了
- No! - Take cover, child.
- 不！ - 找掩護，孩子！
Now switch to Kryptonite.
馬上換成綠色水晶!
Kryptonite.
綠色水晶
Go to Robin's Revenge!
復仇的知更鳥！
Show's over, motherfuckers.
表演結束了，混蛋
Yeah! I think I'm in love with her, dude.
我想我已經愛上她了
She looks like she's about 11 years old, but...
她看起來只有11歲，但是…
I can wait! I solemnly vow to save myself for her.
我可以等，我發誓 我會把我的第一次留給她
That should be really difficult for you. Are you okay?
- 我看很難 - 還好嗎？
Yeah.
嗯
Good job.
好樣的
I'm so proud of you, baby doll.
你是我的驕傲，孩子
Are you okay?
沒事吧？
But getting shot, Daddy, it hurt a lot more than when you did it.
我中彈了，老爸 比你打我時痛多了
That's 'cause I used low velocity rounds, child.
那是因為我用的低速手槍，孩子
You're the kindest daddy in the whole world.
你是全世界最棒的老爸
No, I just...
我只是…
I love you.
我愛你
I love you, too, Daddy.
我也愛你，爸爸
Sleep tight.
晚安
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字？
I mean your real name.
我是說，你的真名
A superhero never reveals his true identity.
超級英雄從不透露她的真實身份
What? Look, you can't go on...
聽著，你不能繼續…
However you lived before,
不管你以前的生活如何
it's over.
都過去了
Is there anybody else? Your family or...
還有別人嗎？別的親人？
Look, I can take care of myself.
我能照顧自己
I saved your sorry ass.
我救了你的小命
What about money, huh? All right, 'cause you got to think long term.
你有錢嗎？ 因為你要有長遠打算
I've got $3 million in a suitcase.
我箱子埵酗T百萬美元
That "long term" enough for you?
對你來說，夠長遠了吧？
It's not all about the money.
不全是錢的事
I owe you.
是我欠你的
If it wasn't for you, I'd be dead.
要不是你，我就死了
And if it wasn't for you,
要不是你
my dad wouldn't be.
我爸爸不會死
Look,
聽著
pack up whatever you need and we'll go back to my place.
收拾一下你的東西 然後去我家
I just need to clean my...
我想我得去洗一下
Just go.
去吧
I meant like pajamas and clothes and stuff. You can't take that stuff to my house.
我的意思是，收拾睡衣，還有外套什麼的 你不能帶這些東西去我家
You know what my dad really would have wanted?
知道我爸爸的願望是什麼嗎？
He would have wanted me to finish what we started.
他希望我能完成使命
And that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
我會繼續幹下去
Is this Frank D'Amico's place?
這是弗蘭克·達米科的地盤嗎？
All that security?
那麼多保安
- Are you crazy? - My mom already died for nothing.
- 你瘋了嗎？ - 我媽媽已經白白死去了
So I'm sure as hell not gonna let my dad die for nothing, too.
所以，我一定不能讓爸爸也白白犧牲
You can't do this on your own.
你不能孤軍奮戰
Exactly.
不錯
Do you wanna deal with owing my dad?
你想還債嗎？
Then shut the hell up and pick your weapon.
那就閉上嘴，拿起武器
Is that what I think it is?
這不是真的吧？
Damn straight.
如假包換
And you better start reading the instructions,
你最好看看說明書
'cause you're gonna be using it in about five minutes.
因為再過五分鐘你就要用它了
Yo, listen up. We got five minutes, then I want you back on your posts.
聽著，五分鐘之後回到各自崗位
And don't leave a mess.
把這埵洵B乾淨
- Everything okay? - Everything's all right, boss.
- 一切正常？ - 一切正常
I can't believe I got my gun back. Look at that.
不敢相信我的槍又回來了 看
You know, it's not the...
你知道那不是…
Let her in.
讓她進來
It's a little kid. What's the matter with you?
只是個小孩 你怎麼了？
You okay, sweetheart?
你沒事吧，寶貝？
I...
我…
I lost my mommy and daddy.
我找不到爸爸媽媽了
You want to use my cell phone?
用我的電話吧？
Now can you remember the number?
你記得號碼嗎？
Help!
救命！
Had I ever been a real superhero?
我做過真正的超級英雄嗎？
The most I'd ever had to offer the world was good intentions
我對這個世界作出的最大的貢獻是
and a slightly elevated capacity to take a kicking.
我的善意以及被誇大的能力
With no power comes no responsibility.
沒有能力，就沒有責任
Except that wasn't true.
只不過這麼說並不正確
- Did you hear that? - Holy shit.
- 聽到了嗎？ - 媽的
Take cover, please.
掩護
Shit.
靠
What the fuck?
怎麼回事？
Get in here. Help me out!
我在這兒，救我出去！
Holy fuck, Fashion, everybody's dead.
他媽的，所有人都死了！
She's behind the counter. She's out of ammo, okay?
她在櫃子後面，她沒子彈了
Do you think they got them?
你覺得他們抓到她了嗎?
If they didn't, he will.
抓不住的話，還有他
Get out there.
給我出去
Now?
現在？
Yeah, now.
對，現在
What the fuck is going on?
現在什麼情況？
We got her trapped. She's unarmed.
我們困住她了，不過她還活著
So what in the hell are you guys waiting for?
那你們還在等什麼？
- Go get her. - Go on, man.
- 去抓住她 - 去啊
- I ain't got no fucking gun.
我只有一支槍，我不能去
I'm not going in.
我不去
You do now.
快去
Now move.
快
Fuck this shit. I'm getting the bazooka.
媽的，我去拿火箭筒
Bazooka?
火箭筒？
It's only me, boss. Everything's under control.
別緊張，是我 一切都在掌控之中
Under control? You're grabbing a fucking bazooka, you dumbass.
掌控之中？ 你這混蛋拿著火箭筒做什麼？
Sir?
頭兒？
Do it.
去吧
I always wanted to say this.
我一直想說
Say hello to my little friend!
跟我的小朋友打個招呼
Holy shit.
他媽的
That is one weird-sounding bazooka.
這個火箭筒的聲音有點奇怪
Stu!
斯圖！
Fuck!
靠！
Get him.
搞定他
Playtime's over, kid.
遊戲時間結束了，孩子
I never play.
我從來不玩遊戲
Oh, really?
真的嗎？
Ruin my business, huh?
毀我的生意？
Kill every single fucking guy on my payroll?
殺我的人？
God, I wish I had a son like you.
真希望我的兒子也能像你這樣
Time for a family reunion.
家人團聚的時候到了
Hey.
嘿
Why don't you pick on someone your own size?
為什麼不找個身材跟你差不多的對手
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
- 還好嗎？ - 沒事
Time to go home.
該回家了
Thanks, Kick-Ass.
謝謝你，海扁王
My daddy,
我爸爸
he would have been proud of both of us.
他會為我們感到驕傲的
Dave.
戴夫
Dave Lizewski.
戴夫·萊澤斯基
I know that, dumbass.
我知道，蠢驢
Mindy.
明迪
Mindy Macready.
明迪·麥克堶}
- Have a good day. Bye. - Bye.
再見
Mindy moved in with Marcus, and he enrolled her at my school.
明迪搬去跟馬庫斯一起住了 在我們學校上學
- Bye. - Good luck.
- 再見 - 好運
First school she'd ever been to, on the promise that I'd look out for her.
這是她第一次上學 我答應會照顧她
Not that she needed me to.
倒不是因為她需要我
Hey, new kid.
嘿，新來的
Hi.
嗨
Lunch money.
午餐錢
Now.
快點
Kick-Ass was gone, but not forgotten.
海扁王走了，但他沒有被遺忘
And my world was much safer with all the new superheroes.
有了這些新的超級英雄 我的世界變得更加安全
They said I was their inspiration,
他們說靈感來自於我
but all I did was make a door into a world I'd dreamed about
但我所做的 只是打開了通往新世界的大門
since I was a little kid.
一個我從小就夢想的世界
A world full of superheroes, huh?
一個充滿超級英雄的世界
As a great man once said,
正如一位偉人曾經所說
"Wait till they get a load of me."
等著受死吧